<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fear on Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/fear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fear on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/fear/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Carrey Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carrey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carrey/</guid>
      <description>What’s yours? How will you serve the world? What do they need that your talent can provide? That’s all you have to figure out. As someone who has done what you are about to go do, I can tell you from experience, the effect you have on others is the most valuable currency there is.
That peace that we’re after, lies somewhere beyond personality, beyond the perception of others, beyond invention and disguise, even beyond effort itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jordan on Fear</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</guid>
      <description>I never looked at the consequences of missing a big shot. Why? Because when you think about the consequences, you always think of a negative result. Some people get frozen by the fear of failure. They get it from peers or from just thinking about the possibility of negative results. They might be afraid of looking bad or being embarrassed. I realized that if I was going to achieve anything in life I had to be aggressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike - On Being Scared</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</guid>
      <description>Too often we are scared. Too often we are scared. Scared of what we might not be able to do. Scared of what people might think if we tried. We let our fears stand in the way of our hopes. We say no when we want to say yes. We sit quietly when we want to scream. And we shout at others, when we should keep our mouths shut. Why?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
