<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perspective on Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/perspective/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Perspective on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2017; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/perspective/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Watts - Acceptance of Death</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattsdeath/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattsdeath/</guid>
      <description>Now there really isn’t anything radically wrong with being sick or with dying. Who said you’re supposed to survive? Who gave you the idea that it’s a gas to go on and on and on?
And we can’t say that it’s a good thing for everything to go on living. In a very simple demonstration that if we enable everybody to go on living, we overcrowd ourselves.
Why else would we have children?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Watts - Choice</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</guid>
      <description>“You do not know where your decisions come from, they pop up like hiccups. People have a great deal of anxiety about making decisions, ‘Did I think this over long enough? Did I take enough data into consideration?’
And if you think it through you find you never could take enough data into consideration, the data for a decision in any given situation is infinite. So what you do is you go through the motions of thinking about out what you will do about this, but worriers are people who think of all the variables beyond their control, and what might happen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Chaplin: Speech in The Great Dictator</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/chaplin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/chaplin/</guid>
      <description> Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Bros Creed</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dutchbros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dutchbros/</guid>
      <description>To be so strong that nothing can disturb your peace of mind;
to talk health, happiness and prosperity to every person you meet;
to make all your friends feel there is something in them;
to look at the sunny side of everything and make your optimism come true;
to think only the best, to work only for the best and expect only the best;
to be just as enthusiastic about the success of others as you are about your own;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Carlin – The Illusion Of Choice</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carlinchoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carlinchoice/</guid>
      <description> Well, we like war. We like war. We are a war like people. We like war because we are good at it. You know, why we are good at it, because we get a lot of practice. This country is only 200 years old and already we’ve had 10 major wars. The average a major war every 20 years in this country.
Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen Keller - Three Days to See (1933)</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was visited by a very good friend who had just returned from a long walk in the woods, and I asked her what she had observed. “Nothing in particular,” she replied. I might have been incredulous had I not been accustomed to such responses, for long ago I became convinced that the seeing see little.
How was it possible, I asked myself, to walk for an hour through the woods and see nothing worthy of note?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Fry on Everything</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/fry/</guid>
      <description> Ego-centric: If you say I all of the time. Be honestly interested in other people. And much more.
Link:  Stephen Fry on Everything  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Laugh Often and Much</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/emerson/</guid>
      <description>To laugh often and much; To win the respect of intelligent people and the affection of children; To earn the appreciation of honest critics and endure the betrayal of false friends; To appreciate beauty, to find the best in others; To leave the world a bit better, whether by a healthy child, a garden patch, or a redeemed social condition; To know even one life has breathed easier because you have lived.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>