<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2017, Brown; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>George Saunders Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/saunders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/saunders/</guid>
      <description>What I regret most in my life are failures of kindness.
Those moments when another human being was there, in front of me, suffering, and I responded&amp;hellip;sensibly. Reservedly. Mildly.
Or, to look at it from the other end of the telescope: Who, in your life, do you remember most fondly, with the most undeniable feelings of warmth? Those who were kindest to you, I bet.
It&amp;rsquo;s a little facile, maybe, and certainly hard to implement, but I&amp;rsquo;d say, as a goal in life, you could do worse than: Try to be kinder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning of a New Day</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/newday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/newday/</guid>
      <description>This is the beginning of a new day I have been given this day to use as I will. I can waste it or use it for good. What I do today is important because I am exchanging a day of my life for it. When tomorrow comes, this day will be gone forever. Leaving something in its place I have traded for it. I want it to be a gain, not loss; good, not evil; success, not failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Watts - Choice</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</guid>
      <description>“You do not know where your decisions come from, they pop up like hiccups. People have a great deal of anxiety about making decisions, ‘Did I think this over long enough? Did I take enough data into consideration?’
And if you think it through you find you never could take enough data into consideration, the data for a decision in any given situation is infinite. So what you do is you go through the motions of thinking about out what you will do about this, but worriers are people who think of all the variables beyond their control, and what might happen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/page/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/page/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer  Your disclaimer text here NOTE:Some information in this website might be copied from other websites. If you see something is your copyright or something should not belong here, please feel free to contact me. I will remove necessary parts.     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/page/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/page/license/</guid>
      <description>LICENSE  Unless otherwise mentioned code from this blog can used as per MIT or Apache 2.0 license.     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/page/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/page/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Other sites that I like:  Graduation Wisdom LYBIO.NET UpWorthy  Setup Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
Have questions or suggestions? Feel free to open an issue on GitHub or ask me on Twitter.
Thanks for reading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Watts - Acceptance of Death</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattsdeath/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattsdeath/</guid>
      <description>Now there really isn’t anything radically wrong with being sick or with dying. Who said you’re supposed to survive? Who gave you the idea that it’s a gas to go on and on and on?
And we can’t say that it’s a good thing for everything to go on living. In a very simple demonstration that if we enable everybody to go on living, we overcrowd ourselves.
Why else would we have children?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arnold Schwarzenegger USC Commencement Address</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/arnold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/arnold/</guid>
      <description>6 Rules 
1. Trust yourself  Dig deep down, who do you want to be?  2. Break the rules  It is impossible to be a maverick or true original if you don’t break the rules. You have to think outside of the box.  3. Don’t be afraid to fail  You can’t always win, but don’t be afraid of making decisions. Don’t get paralyzed by failure or you won’t push yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Motivational</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/bestmotiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/bestmotiv/</guid>
      <description> Effort and productivity. It&amp;rsquo;s not all about effort either. It&amp;rsquo;s about how you do the activity too. What are you going to do today? BUT, more importantly, how are you going to do it?
Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Chaplin: Speech in The Great Dictator</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/chaplin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/chaplin/</guid>
      <description> Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Quit</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dontquit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dontquit/</guid>
      <description>When things go wrong, as they sometimes will, When the road you&amp;rsquo;re trudging seems all uphill, When funds are low and the debts are high, And you want to smile but you have to sigh, When care is pressing you down a bit, Rest if you must, but don&amp;rsquo;t you quit.

Life is queer with its twists and turns, As every one of us sometimes learns, And many a failure turns about, When he might have won if he&amp;rsquo;d stuck it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Carlin – The Illusion Of Choice</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carlinchoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carlinchoice/</guid>
      <description> Well, we like war. We like war. We are a war like people. We like war because we are good at it. You know, why we are good at it, because we get a lot of practice. This country is only 200 years old and already we’ve had 10 major wars. The average a major war every 20 years in this country.
Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen Keller - Three Days to See (1933)</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was visited by a very good friend who had just returned from a long walk in the woods, and I asked her what she had observed. “Nothing in particular,” she replied. I might have been incredulous had I not been accustomed to such responses, for long ago I became convinced that the seeing see little.
How was it possible, I asked myself, to walk for an hour through the woods and see nothing worthy of note?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Smith on Death from Joe Rogan Experience</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/smith/</guid>
      <description>Play it with passion. Death – in a world where you’re going to die, why not? What do you have to lose? His dad died screaming.  There&amp;rsquo;s no point in not trying to accomplish every dream I&amp;rsquo;ve got.   Chasing Whimsies  At the end it might just be get in the box, you had your chance.
 Chase it all down; big and small. Go after your dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jordan on Fear</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</guid>
      <description>I never looked at the consequences of missing a big shot. Why? Because when you think about the consequences, you always think of a negative result. Some people get frozen by the fear of failure. They get it from peers or from just thinking about the possibility of negative results. They might be afraid of looking bad or being embarrassed. I realized that if I was going to achieve anything in life I had to be aggressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike - On Being Scared</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</guid>
      <description>Too often we are scared. Too often we are scared. Scared of what we might not be able to do. Scared of what people might think if we tried. We let our fears stand in the way of our hopes. We say no when we want to say yes. We sit quietly when we want to scream. And we shout at others, when we should keep our mouths shut. Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ray Lewis on Effort</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lewis/</guid>
      <description> Effort is between you and you. Ain&amp;rsquo;t nobody else can give you effort. Effort is what&amp;rsquo;s inside. Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Fry on Everything</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/fry/</guid>
      <description> Ego-centric: If you say I all of the time. Be honestly interested in other people. And much more.
Link:  Stephen Fry on Everything  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs Stanford Commencement Address</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jobs/</guid>
      <description>3 Stories 
1. Connecting the dots  Took a calligraphy class. 10 years later it all came back to him and used that knowledge in the Mac. Impossible to connect the dots looking forward. You have to trust that the dots will somehow connect in your future.  If you simply do enough things and show curiosity and the ability to learn that things eventually fit together in some fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Water: David Foster Wallace Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wallace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wallace/</guid>
      <description>Learning how to think really means learning how to exercise some control over how and what you think. It means being conscious and aware enough to choose what you pay attention to and to choose how you construct meaning from experience.
The capital-T Truth is about life BEFORE death. It is about the real value of a real education, which has almost nothing to do with knowledge, and everything to do with simple awareness; awareness of what is so real and essential, so hidden in plain sight all around us, all the time, that we have to keep reminding ourselves over and over:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncomfortable vs Exhaustion</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/exhaustion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/exhaustion/</guid>
      <description> How hungry are you to improve?
How big is your appetite for success?
What are you willing to do you reach your dreams?
Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>