<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speech on Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/categories/speech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speech on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/categories/speech/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Motivational</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/bestmotiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/bestmotiv/</guid>
      <description> Effort and productivity.  It&amp;rsquo;s not all about effort either.
It&amp;rsquo;s about how you do the activity too.
You can be doing the right activity, but going through the motions.
Productivity is a combination of effort and focusing on doing the activity right.
What are you going to do today?
BUT, more importantly, how are you going to do it?
 Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Sagan - The Pale Blue Dot</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/sagan-dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/sagan-dot/</guid>
      <description>Look again at that dot. That&amp;rsquo;s here. That&amp;rsquo;s home. That&amp;rsquo;s us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &amp;ldquo;superstar,&amp;rdquo; every &amp;ldquo;supreme leader,&amp;rdquo; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there&amp;ndash;on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Chaplin: Speech in The Great Dictator</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/chaplin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/chaplin/</guid>
      <description>We all want to help one another. Human beings are like that. We want to live by each other’s happiness - not by each other’s misery. We don’t want to hate and despise one another. In this world there is room for everyone. And the good earth is rich and can provide for everyone. The way of life can be free and beautiful, but we have lost the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dare to be Great</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dareto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dareto/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Imma show you, how great I am. Last night, I cut the light off in my bedroom and was in bed before the room was dark. Imma show you, how great I am. Only last week, I murdered a rock, injured a stone, hospitalised a brick. I&amp;rsquo;m so mean, I make medicine sick. Imma show you, how great I am. This kid&amp;rsquo;s gonna be the best kid in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Carlin – The Illusion Of Choice</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carlinchoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carlinchoice/</guid>
      <description> Well, we like war. We like war. We are a war like people. We like war because we are good at it. You know, why we are good at it, because we get a lot of practice. This country is only 200 years old and already we’ve had 10 major wars. The average a major war every 20 years in this country.
Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ray Lewis on Effort</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lewis/</guid>
      <description> Effort is between you and you. Ain&amp;rsquo;t nobody else can give you effort. Effort is what&amp;rsquo;s inside. Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncomfortable vs Exhaustion</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/exhaustion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/exhaustion/</guid>
      <description> How hungry are you to improve?
How big is your appetite for success?
What are you willing to do you reach your dreams?
Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winning is a habit (Vince Lombardi)</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lombardi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lombardi/</guid>
      <description> Winning is not a one time thing. It&amp;rsquo;s an all the time thing. You don&amp;rsquo;t win once in a while and you don&amp;rsquo;t do things right once in while. You do them right all of the time. Winnning is a habit.
Appreciate the grind, the discipline, and to win, and to win, and to win.
Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Watts - Acceptance of Death</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattsdeath/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattsdeath/</guid>
      <description>Now there really isn’t anything radically wrong with being sick or with dying. Who said you’re supposed to survive? Who gave you the idea that it’s a gas to go on and on and on?
And we can’t say that it’s a good thing for everything to go on living. In a very simple demonstration that if we enable everybody to go on living, we overcrowd ourselves.
Why else would we have children?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Watts - Choice</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</guid>
      <description>“You do not know where your decisions come from, they pop up like hiccups. People have a great deal of anxiety about making decisions, ‘Did I think this over long enough? Did I take enough data into consideration?’
And if you think it through you find you never could take enough data into consideration, the data for a decision in any given situation is infinite. So what you do is you go through the motions of thinking about out what you will do about this, but worriers are people who think of all the variables beyond their control, and what might happen!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
