<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life Advice on Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/life-advice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life Advice on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/life-advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Things You Should Give Up If You Want To Be Successful</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/13thingsyoushouldgiveup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/13thingsyoushouldgiveup/</guid>
      <description>Somebody once told me the definition of hell: “On your last day on earth, the person you became will meet the person you could have become.”
 — Anonymous
13 Things You Should Give Up If You Want To Be Successful.
 Give Up On The Unhealthy Lifestyle
“Take care of your body. It’s the only place you have to live.” — Jim Rohn
 Give Up The Short-term Mindset</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arnold Schwarzenegger USC Commencement Address</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/arnold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/arnold/</guid>
      <description>6 Rules 
1. Trust yourself  Dig deep down, who do you really want to be? Not your parents or teachers, but you.  2. Break the rules  It is impossible to be a maverick or true original if you don’t break the rules. You have to think outside of the box.  3. Don’t be afraid to fail  You can’t always win, but don’t be afraid of making decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio Links</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/audio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/audio/</guid>
      <description>  Links to over a dozen audio clips on various topics.
           Links.  Full Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bargained with Life for a Penny</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/penny/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/penny/</guid>
      <description>“I bargained with Life for a penny,
And Life would pay no more,
However I begged at evening
When I counted my scanty store;
For Life is just an employer,
He gives you what you ask,
But once you have set the wages,
Why, you must bear the task.
I worked for a menial&amp;rsquo;s hire,
Only to learn, dismayed,
That any wage I had asked of Life,
Life would have paid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning of a New Day</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/newday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/newday/</guid>
      <description>This is the beginning of a new day I have been given this day to use as I will. I can waste it or use it for good. What I do today is important because I am exchanging a day of my life for it. When tomorrow comes, this day will be gone forever. Leaving something in its place I have traded for it. I want it to be a gain, not loss; good, not evil; success, not failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Motivational</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/bestmotiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/bestmotiv/</guid>
      <description>  Effort and productivity.  It&amp;rsquo;s not all about effort either.
It&amp;rsquo;s about how you do the activity too.
You can be doing the right activity, but going through the motions.
Productivity is a combination of effort and focusing on doing the activity right.
What are you going to do today?
BUT, more importantly, how are you going to do it?
 Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Sagan - The Pale Blue Dot</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/sagan-dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/sagan-dot/</guid>
      <description>Pale Blue Dot from Richard G on Vimeo.
 -- Look again at that dot. That&amp;rsquo;s here. That&amp;rsquo;s home. That&amp;rsquo;s us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &amp;ldquo;superstar,&amp;rdquo; every &amp;ldquo;supreme leader,&amp;rdquo; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there&amp;ndash;on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dare to be Great</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dareto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dareto/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Imma show you, how great I am. Last night, I cut the light off in my bedroom and was in bed before the room was dark. Imma show you, how great I am. Only last week, I murdered a rock, injured a stone, hospitalised a brick. I&amp;rsquo;m so mean, I make medicine sick. Imma show you, how great I am. This kid&amp;rsquo;s gonna be the best kid in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Quit</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dontquit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dontquit/</guid>
      <description>When things go wrong, as they sometimes will, When the road you&amp;rsquo;re trudging seems all uphill, When funds are low and the debts are high, And you want to smile but you have to sigh, When care is pressing you down a bit, Rest if you must, but don&amp;rsquo;t you quit.

Life is queer with its twists and turns, As every one of us sometimes learns, And many a failure turns about, When he might have won if he&amp;rsquo;d stuck it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Bros Creed</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dutchbros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dutchbros/</guid>
      <description>To be so strong that nothing can disturb your peace of mind;
to talk health, happiness and prosperity to every person you meet;
to make all your friends feel there is something in them;
to look at the sunny side of everything and make your optimism come true;
to think only the best, to work only for the best and expect only the best;
to be just as enthusiastic about the success of others as you are about your own;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Saunders Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/saunders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/saunders/</guid>
      <description>What I regret most in my life are failures of kindness.
Those moments when another human being was there, in front of me, suffering, and I responded&amp;hellip;sensibly. Reservedly. Mildly.
Or, to look at it from the other end of the telescope: Who, in your life, do you remember most fondly, with the most undeniable feelings of warmth? Those who were kindest to you, I bet.
It&amp;rsquo;s a little facile, maybe, and certainly hard to implement, but I&amp;rsquo;d say, as a goal in life, you could do worse than: Try to be kinder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen Keller - Three Days to See (1933)</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was visited by a very good friend who had just returned from a long walk in the woods, and I asked her what she had observed. “Nothing in particular,” she replied. I might have been incredulous had I not been accustomed to such responses, for long ago I became convinced that the seeing see little.
How was it possible, I asked myself, to walk for an hour through the woods and see nothing worthy of note?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Smith on Death from Joe Rogan Experience</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/smith/</guid>
      <description>Play it with passion. One life, you die at the end. We hope for candyland. But it could be as simple as get in a box and stay there for eternity. You had your shot, you&amp;rsquo;re a computer, we shut you down and you&amp;rsquo;re finished.
Regardless of the reality of candyland, if this is our one shot on Earth; it really behooves you to always shoot for your dreams every time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jordan on Fear</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</guid>
      <description>I never looked at the consequences of missing a big shot. Why? Because when you think about the consequences, you always think of a negative result. Some people get frozen by the fear of failure. They get it from peers or from just thinking about the possibility of negative results. They might be afraid of looking bad or being embarrassed. I realized that if I was going to achieve anything in life I had to be aggressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike - On Being Scared</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</guid>
      <description>Too often we are scared. Too often we are scared. Scared of what we might not be able to do. Scared of what people might think if we tried. We let our fears stand in the way of our hopes. We say no when we want to say yes. We sit quietly when we want to scream. And we shout at others, when we should keep our mouths shut. Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ray Lewis on Effort</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lewis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/lewis/</guid>
      <description> Effort is between you and you. Ain&amp;rsquo;t nobody else can give you effort. Effort is what&amp;rsquo;s inside.  Links.  Full YouTube Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Fry on Everything</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/fry/</guid>
      <description> Ego-centric: If you say I all of the time. Be honestly interested in other people. And much more.
 Link:  Stephen Fry on Everything  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Laugh Often and Much</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/emerson/</guid>
      <description>To laugh often and much; To win the respect of intelligent people and the affection of children; To earn the appreciation of honest critics and endure the betrayal of false friends; To appreciate beauty, to find the best in others; To leave the world a bit better, whether by a healthy child, a garden patch, or a redeemed social condition; To know even one life has breathed easier because you have lived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffet - Your Only Car In Life</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/buffet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/buffet/</guid>
      <description>“When I was sixteen, I had just two things on my mind - girls and cars. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t very good with girls. So I thought about cars. I thought about girls, too, but I had more luck with cars.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say that when I turned sixteen, a genie had appeared to me. And that genie said, &amp;lsquo;Warren, I&amp;rsquo;m going to give you the car of your choice. It&amp;rsquo;ll be here tomorrow morning with a big bow tied on it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>