<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Commencement Speech on Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/categories/commencement-speech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Commencement Speech on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2017; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/categories/commencement-speech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arnold Schwarzenegger USC Commencement Address</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/arnold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/arnold/</guid>
      <description>6 Rules 
1. Trust yourself  Dig deep down, who do you want to be?  2. Break the rules  It is impossible to be a maverick or true original if you don’t break the rules. You have to think outside of the box.  3. Don’t be afraid to fail  You can’t always win, but don’t be afraid of making decisions. Don’t get paralyzed by failure or you won’t push yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Foster Wallace: This Is Water Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wallace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wallace/</guid>
      <description>Learning how to think really means learning how to exercise some control over how and what you think. It means being conscious and aware enough to choose what you pay attention to and to choose how you construct meaning from experience.
The capital-T Truth is about life BEFORE death. It is about the real value of a real education, which has almost nothing to do with knowledge, and everything to do with simple awareness; awareness of what is so real and essential, so hidden in plain sight all around us, all the time, that we have to keep reminding ourselves over and over:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Saunders Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/saunders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/saunders/</guid>
      <description>What I regret most in my life are failures of kindness.
Those moments when another human being was there, in front of me, suffering, and I responded&amp;hellip;sensibly. Reservedly. Mildly.
Or, to look at it from the other end of the telescope: Who, in your life, do you remember most fondly, with the most undeniable feelings of warmth? Those who were kindest to you, I bet.
It&amp;rsquo;s a little facile, maybe, and certainly hard to implement, but I&amp;rsquo;d say, as a goal in life, you could do worse than: Try to be kinder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Carrey Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carrey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carrey/</guid>
      <description>The affect you have on others is the most valuable currency there is.
Your need for acceptance can make you invisible in this world. Don&amp;rsquo;t let anything stand in the way of this light that shines through this form. Risk being seen in all of your glory.
You&amp;rsquo;ll only ever have two choices: love or fear. Choose love and don&amp;rsquo;t ever let fear turn you away from your playful heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs Stanford Commencement Address</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jobs/</guid>
      <description>3 Stories 
1. Connecting the dots  He took a calligraphy class at Reed College. 10 years later it all came back to him and used that knowledge in the Mac. It&amp;rsquo;s impossible to connect the dots looking forward. You have to trust that the dots will somehow connect in your future.  If you simply do enough things and show curiosity with the ability to learn, eventually they&amp;rsquo;ll fit together in some fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>