<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Choice on Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/choice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Choice on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/tags/choice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Things You Should Give Up If You Want To Be Successful</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/13thingsyoushouldgiveup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/13thingsyoushouldgiveup/</guid>
      <description>Somebody once told me the definition of hell: “On your last day on earth, the person you became will meet the person you could have become.”
 — Anonymous
13 Things You Should Give Up If You Want To Be Successful.
 Give Up On The Unhealthy Lifestyle
“Take care of your body. It’s the only place you have to live.” — Jim Rohn
 Give Up The Short-term Mindset</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio Links</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/audio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/audio/</guid>
      <description>  Links to over a dozen audio clips on various topics.
           Links.  Full Link.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bargained with Life for a Penny</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/penny/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/penny/</guid>
      <description>“I bargained with Life for a penny,
And Life would pay no more,
However I begged at evening
When I counted my scanty store;
For Life is just an employer,
He gives you what you ask,
But once you have set the wages,
Why, you must bear the task.
I worked for a menial&amp;rsquo;s hire,
Only to learn, dismayed,
That any wage I had asked of Life,
Life would have paid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Foster Wallace: This Is Water Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wallace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wallace/</guid>
      <description>Learning how to think really means learning how to exercise some control over how and what you think. It means being conscious and aware enough to choose what you pay attention to and to choose how you construct meaning from experience.
The capital-T Truth is about life BEFORE death. It is about the real value of a real education, which has almost nothing to do with knowledge, and everything to do with simple awareness; awareness of what is so real and essential, so hidden in plain sight all around us, all the time, that we have to keep reminding ourselves over and over:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Carrey Commencement Speech</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carrey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/carrey/</guid>
      <description>What’s yours? How will you serve the world? What do they need that your talent can provide? That’s all you have to figure out. As someone who has done what you are about to go do, I can tell you from experience, the effect you have on others is the most valuable currency there is.
That peace that we’re after, lies somewhere beyond personality, beyond the perception of others, beyond invention and disguise, even beyond effort itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffet - Your Only Car In Life</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/buffet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/buffet/</guid>
      <description>“When I was sixteen, I had just two things on my mind - girls and cars. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t very good with girls. So I thought about cars. I thought about girls, too, but I had more luck with cars.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say that when I turned sixteen, a genie had appeared to me. And that genie said, &amp;lsquo;Warren, I&amp;rsquo;m going to give you the car of your choice. It&amp;rsquo;ll be here tomorrow morning with a big bow tied on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Watts - Choice</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/wattschoice/</guid>
      <description>“You do not know where your decisions come from, they pop up like hiccups. People have a great deal of anxiety about making decisions, ‘Did I think this over long enough? Did I take enough data into consideration?’
And if you think it through you find you never could take enough data into consideration, the data for a decision in any given situation is infinite. So what you do is you go through the motions of thinking about out what you will do about this, but worriers are people who think of all the variables beyond their control, and what might happen!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>