<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Text on Just Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/categories/text/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Text on Just Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/categories/text/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>13 Things You Should Give Up If You Want To Be Successful</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/13thingsyoushouldgiveup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/13thingsyoushouldgiveup/</guid>
      <description>Somebody once told me the definition of hell: “On your last day on earth, the person you became will meet the person you could have become.”
 — Anonymous
13 Things You Should Give Up If You Want To Be Successful.
 Give Up On The Unhealthy Lifestyle
“Take care of your body. It’s the only place you have to live.” — Jim Rohn
 Give Up The Short-term Mindset</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning of a New Day</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/newday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/newday/</guid>
      <description>This is the beginning of a new day I have been given this day to use as I will. I can waste it or use it for good. What I do today is important because I am exchanging a day of my life for it. When tomorrow comes, this day will be gone forever. Leaving something in its place I have traded for it. I want it to be a gain, not loss; good, not evil; success, not failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Quit</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dontquit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dontquit/</guid>
      <description>When things go wrong, as they sometimes will, When the road you&amp;rsquo;re trudging seems all uphill, When funds are low and the debts are high, And you want to smile but you have to sigh, When care is pressing you down a bit, Rest if you must, but don&amp;rsquo;t you quit.

Life is queer with its twists and turns, As every one of us sometimes learns, And many a failure turns about, When he might have won if he&amp;rsquo;d stuck it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Bros Creed</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dutchbros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/dutchbros/</guid>
      <description>To be so strong that nothing can disturb your peace of mind;
to talk health, happiness and prosperity to every person you meet;
to make all your friends feel there is something in them;
to look at the sunny side of everything and make your optimism come true;
to think only the best, to work only for the best and expect only the best;
to be just as enthusiastic about the success of others as you are about your own;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen Keller - Three Days to See (1933)</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/keller/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was visited by a very good friend who had just returned from a long walk in the woods, and I asked her what she had observed. “Nothing in particular,” she replied. I might have been incredulous had I not been accustomed to such responses, for long ago I became convinced that the seeing see little.
How was it possible, I asked myself, to walk for an hour through the woods and see nothing worthy of note?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jordan on Fear</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/jodanfear/</guid>
      <description>I never looked at the consequences of missing a big shot. Why? Because when you think about the consequences, you always think of a negative result. Some people get frozen by the fear of failure. They get it from peers or from just thinking about the possibility of negative results. They might be afraid of looking bad or being embarrassed. I realized that if I was going to achieve anything in life I had to be aggressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike - On Being Scared</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/nike/</guid>
      <description>Too often we are scared. Too often we are scared. Scared of what we might not be able to do. Scared of what people might think if we tried. We let our fears stand in the way of our hopes. We say no when we want to say yes. We sit quietly when we want to scream. And we shout at others, when we should keep our mouths shut. Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Laugh Often and Much</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/emerson/</guid>
      <description>To laugh often and much; To win the respect of intelligent people and the affection of children; To earn the appreciation of honest critics and endure the betrayal of false friends; To appreciate beauty, to find the best in others; To leave the world a bit better, whether by a healthy child, a garden patch, or a redeemed social condition; To know even one life has breathed easier because you have lived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffet - Your Only Car In Life</title>
      <link>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/buffet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbro28.github.io/thoughts/post/buffet/</guid>
      <description>“When I was sixteen, I had just two things on my mind - girls and cars. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t very good with girls. So I thought about cars. I thought about girls, too, but I had more luck with cars.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say that when I turned sixteen, a genie had appeared to me. And that genie said, &amp;lsquo;Warren, I&amp;rsquo;m going to give you the car of your choice. It&amp;rsquo;ll be here tomorrow morning with a big bow tied on it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>